Welcome back.
So in this section, we are going to do a God leap practical session.
So what we are going to do is we are going to overlay the God's Settings app with an overlay using Kahlua.
OK, so let's go ahead.
OK.
So I'll just tell you exactly what I am planning to do.
So I have the emulator open here and I have a terminal option here.
OK.
So let me enable the resource overlay now.
Because.
OK.
So I had just enabled the overlay now, and you can see the color, background color and the title code
changed.
OK.
Don't worry about the formatting.
So this is just a demonstration.
Don't learn formatting from me.
So I am very bad at that.
So just go ahead and make your own formatting and design it as best as you can.
So this is the best I could do, actually.
OK.
Just kidding.
So here I have enabled.
And now let's disable that back.
OK and disable it back.
So this the command the command.
Enable and disable virtual show you that later.
So these are the two commands basically enabling and disabling.
OK, so now.
OK, so now I am back in my resourcefully accord, and here this is the simple RRO package which we
which I have just created.
OK, so it's a very simple package and here you could see it has only a resource folder with colors
and styles.
OK.
So inside the colors, you have got these, uh, elements and inside the styles you have this.
So this is basically overlaying the title.
And this is basically overlaying the background color, the color, scroll a scroll bottom and do action
devoid of color.
OK.
So these are the elements which actually exist in Idlib.
And basically what we are doing here is we are overriding the car Dua Lipa resources.
So only the apps which actually uses got UI Lib will be affected by this overlays.
So as we know, car settings is actually using a.
And that's the reason the color of the background color title everything gets changed when we enable
this overlay.
OK, so in order to prove that.
Just quickly show you this element inside cardio.
So if you come up, this is really bad here you have the wireless only here you have the color, the
same file, which we are actually all right.
And just don't click on this.
And if you search for it so you can see it is actually set to black color, which is actually the default
one, which we are seeing here, right?
So when we overlay, it gets changed to the new colour.
Uh, this one.
OK, so behind the scenes, it's basically a small AP case in bilateral dot epic, which actually just
overlays the resources during prime time on top of the existing car settings app.
So in summary, the logic or the overall architecture is quite simple.
So basically it's just overlaying some resources during that time around time onto what if we keep on
top of the game?
OK, so now we have the Stynes.
So as say said it is just the car idle.
I'm just increasing it to eight DSP and the color is this one.
OK, so then let's have a look at that or not.
And this is again a very simple, empty file.
So you have these three new elements.
You got a UI, RRO set name and is the name of the RRO, and then it's got a UI resource territory.
That's a resource that it it's pointing to this folder and then you have the target.
So targeting is actually the applications which you are targeting.
So in my example, I'm only targeting Settings app, but you can target and number of applications.
Yeah, so you just need to add it over here.
Like in case if you want to focus dialer app so you can just give it like this, like this or any any
other app within the car, or you can just give it over here.
OK.
So in for this example, I'm just focusing the Settings app.
OK, but you can try it out with different apps.
Let's run.
OK, so that's about this one.
And it also includes these Scotty White Generator Arrow set.
OK.
And then we have the Android Manifest Court example.
Fine.
So this is again pretty straightforward.
Here you have the package name.
The RRO package name will be taken dynamically when you compile it, so you can just leave it as cities,
actually.
So it will be replaced dynamically during the brief time and the target packages as well will be dynamically,
um, overwritten and during the time.
OK.
So just leave these to other cities and then you have the priority.
So Priority 10 means it's actually off.
So, so to explain that better and just imagine that you have multiple overlays, multiple static overlays.
OK.
So when you have multiple static overlays, a higher number means you have a higher precedence and over
no means you have a lower precedence.
OK.
As simple as that?
And then you have this static.
So each static means you can set.
You can create or less static or not static.
So in this case, I am setting it to not static.
OK.
So then you set an overlay to static.
That means that it is enabled by default.
And it's actually mute, not me.
OK, so that means you cannot actually change that during front time.
So it is actually you cannot enable or disable that.
So in this case, I'm sitting at two phones so that you can change that, OK?
And dynamically.
OK.
Uh, yeah.
OK, then what else?
So then that's done.
Uh, so we covered all the files within the sample RRO package.
OK, now let's go ahead and compile our package, compile our RRO package and install it into the emulator.
OK, so let's.
Close over regulator first and let me check where I am at the moment.
Okay, so I am inside the same bilateral package, and so I am just building it now, um.
Okay, so let's build.
OK, so now the bill is successful and that I have the EPA over here.
So I got a failure earlier, so that was actually due to some, some unnecessary space within them gave
way.
So just make sure that you don't have any unnecessary space between them.
Okay, fine.
OK, so now they because actually generated here.
So now let's copy this part because I need to first open them later.
Yeah.
Then let's start my emulator.
Okay, maybe.
Yeah, this will do okay and let you open a different window.
Mm yeah.
So here I'm just in St...
OK, I have some bank issues, you know, so that I may.
Yeah, so I have some alias Ali alias defined here.
So don't get confused with that.
OK, so I have now installed it.
OK.
So to make it pretty clear, actually, I have some alias defined here.
I have a set of YASYA with which I can have shortcuts.
So that's why I'm using shortcuts all the time.
So now let's uh.
Now the speaker is already installed.
So now let's do.
Let's get into ADB Shell and here let's run the overlay.
Seem to be overly
lest you saw cotton.
So here are our package war settings, so you can see here are our overlays there.
And at the moment, it's actually disabled.
So let's go ahead and enable it.
So to enable, you have to um, you have to give a command overlay, enable you so calm and then the
package name.
So this package was hidden.
So this copy, this is pasted over here.
So I have no doubt enabled it.
So let's come back so I can see that here.
OK.
So now let's let me keep it like this.
So if you want to disable.
So if you want to disable just
disable it like this and it's gone.
OK, so I hope you understood something from this video.
And so just to quickly summarize, so we created this smart package where you have resources, you have
colors, styles and then you have an android or time game and an Android manifest.
So here you have just defined a small runtime overlay, which which is actually overlaying the audio
clip and this back.
This will be enabled only for the packages specified here, as well as the one which uses the Car UI
leap.
So it's actually both.
So you have to specify here that is, of course, true.
So if you specified it here, it has to be.
You seen Corey Wiley.
OK.
So if you specify a package which is actually not using Ailbhe, then this won't work.
Um, OK.
So basically, this is overlaying the resources from the car.
OK.
So I hope that makes sense, and I hope you learn something out of it.
And I have attached all these code with this letter.
Please take it and make your own modifications, make some better styling and enable it.
And in case if you have any trouble in setting it up, please let me know I can help.
Uh, okay, that's it.
Thank you for your time.